global1training.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy & Security Policy

Privacy & Security Policy   
  
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Global1Training Pty Ltd (ACN 18 112 642 485) (“Global1”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [www.global1training.com](http://global1.com.au/) or [www.global1.com.au](http://global1.com.au/) websites ("Sites"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Global1.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using these Sites, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of use](http://global1.com.au/terms-of-use). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of these Sites, or your dealings with these Sites should be directed by e-mail to [info@global1.com.au](mailto:info@global1.com.au). You also contact us at Global1Training Pty Ltd, Suite 1106, Level 11, 100 William St Woolloomooloo NSW 2011.

### Information Collected

When you look at this website, our Internet Service Provider makes a record of your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes:

  * your server address
  * your top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk, etc)
  * the date and time of your visit to the site
  * the pages you accessed and documents downloaded
  * the previous site you have visited
  * the type of browser you are using)

We collect personal information primarily to record appropriate details for any service or order you have placed with us, and also that we may:

  * administer our customer relationships;
  * provide you with information, products or services you have requested;
  * review and assess our products and services;
  * collect and analyse information for marketing and research purposes;
  * assist customers by providing them with information;
  * personalise and customise your experiences with our Sites
  * communicate with you; and
  * provide you with ongoing information about which we believe you may be interested.

We only collect personal information for purposes which are directly related to our functions or activities under [the Privacy Act 1988 (link is external)](http://www.comlaw.gov.au/Series/C2004A03712) (Privacy Act), [Freedom of Information Act 1982 (link is external)](http://www.comlaw.gov.au/Series/C2004A02562) (FOI Act) or the [Australian Information Commissioner Act 2010 (link is external)](http://www.comlaw.gov.au/Series/C2010A00052) (AIC Act), and only when it is necessary for or directly related to such purposes

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### How we use collected information

Gobal1 may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _**To improve customer service**_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _**To personalize user experience**_   
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _**To improve our Site**_   
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _**To process payments**_  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * _**To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature**_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _**To send periodic emails**_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
  * _**To send periodic SMS and MMS messages**_  
We may use the mobile phone number to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in SMS list, they will receive SMS’s that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future SMSs, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each SMS.

The nature of the Internet means that some of your personal information may be transferred, stored, processed or used overseas. This may happen if we outsource certain activities overseas or if transactions, information, services or products have an overseas connection.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilised and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Sites may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### Online Advertising We Use

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to trigger display ads across the Internet. AdWords Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of Global1 website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. 

If you do not wish to participate in our Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting [Google's Ads Preferences Manager (link is external)](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

If other organisations provide support services, we require them to appropriately safeguard the privacy of the information provided to them. Where the personal information we collect is no longer required, we delete the information or permanently de-identify it. We will not otherwise disclose your personal information unless the disclosure:

  * is required by law
  * is authorised by law; or
  * you have consented to our disclosing the information.

### Choice/Opt-Out

If you are a newsletter subscriber, you always have the option of no longer receiving them. At the bottom of each newsletter there is an opt-out option. Simply click on “Please click here to unsubscribe”.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Sites or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Global1 has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
